Dave: It’s really hot.
Would you like a drink? Or some ice cream?
Becca: Yes, why not? Let’s go to the café.
Dave: What kind of ice cream do you want?
Becca: Um… an ice-cream bar if they have it.
Dave: Here you are. One ice-cream bar.
Becca: Thanks, Dave.
Dave: Where do you live?
Becca: I live near here, on Park Road.
And you?
Dave: I live across town, on Lake Street.
What do you do, Becca?
Becca: I’m a journalist.
Dave: Really? How interesting!
Do you work for a newspaper?
Becca: No, for TV.
What about you?
Dave: I’m a teacher.
I’m on vacation now.
Becca: Me too.
Oh! My ice cream.
Dave: Dolly! Bad dog!
I’m really sorry.
Becca: That’s OK.
Dave: Do you want another ice-cream bar?
Becca: No, thanks.
Dave: Are you sure?
I’m really sorry.
Look, let’s have lunch one day.
I know a great place that’s dog-friendly.
Are you free on Saturday?
Becca: Oh, well, OK. Yes.
Thanks.